bankexamsindia.com 2018-12-21

# Privacy Policy

**BankExamsIndia.com respects your privacy**

Bankexamsindia.com takes this Privay policy seriously and strictly adheres to it.Any personal information you provide us including your name,website url,address and email address will not be released,sold or rented to anyone outside bankexamsindia.com

**Usage of Information Collected**

Your email address would be collected if you want to subscribe to our updates posted on this site.Detailed information on unsubscribing from our mailing list is provided with all emails sent to you from us.

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.This site uses [Getclicky ](http://www.getclicky.com/)to automatically receive and record information from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you request.As said,such information will not be released,rented or sold outside of bankexamsindia.com

**Usage of Cookies and Web beacons**

A “cookie” is a small text file placed in your computer and allows bankexamsindia.com to recognise you the next time you visit.Cookies does not contain any of your personal information,and bankexamsindia.com does not use cookies to collect information.These cookies might be collected by 3rd party content providers such as online advertising companies.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Google,as a third party vendor,uses cookies to serve ads on this site.Google's use of the [DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**Privacy policy changes**   
We may update this policy in future.Incase of such an event,the changes will be reflected in this page.If you have any doubts,you can email us at contact[at]bankexamsindia.com (replace [at] with @) 

**Share this** :
